这是份合约
Now that's a contract.
此时  我们定义出我们想要的列名称
At this point, we define the names of the columns we want,
但是我们仍然没有数据库
but we still don't have a database.
为真做一个数据库  我们要去继承 Android 的SQLiteOpenHelper
To actually make a database, we're gong to extend Android's SQLiteOpenHelper.
SQLiteOpenHelper 包含了很棒的工具  用于创建数据库并
SQLiteOpenHelper contains cool stuff to create the database and
帮助我们处理数据库的版本控制
help us handle database versioning.
当未来我们对数据库做一些改变的时候
As we make changes to our database in the future,
它将会帮助我们改动这些表格
tt will help us modify our tables.
对于很多应用来说
For many apps,
在不损失任何数据的前提下更新到新版本是很关键的
being able to upgrade to a new version without data loss is critical.
对于Sunshine数据库来说  我们的目的是确保升级引发的
For Sunshine, we just want to make sure that upgrades in that involve
数据表改变可以平滑的发生
schema changes happen smoothly.
让我们从应用上更近的观察SQLiteOpenHelper
Let's take a look at SQLiteOpenHelper more closely in action.
我们要在WeatherDBHelper类中做些事情  此类是SQLiteOpenHelper的继承
We're going to be working in the WeatherDBHelper class that you've been
given which extends SQLiteOpenHelper.
它包含创建和初始化天气数据库的代码
It contains code to create and initialize the weather database.
让我们试验一下
Let's examine it.
在DbHelper的开始  可以见到我们定义了两个常量
At the beginning of the DbHelper, you can see that we've defined constants for
DATABASE_VERSION 和 DATABASE_NAME
DATABASE_VERSION and DATABASE_NAME.
典型的  DATABASE_VERSION 从版本1开始并且在我们
The DATABASE_VERSION typically starts at version 1 and must be manually
发布带有新数据库表的更新APK时必须手动增加
incremented each time we release an updated APK with a new database schema.
DATABASE_NAME 是文件系统中数据库文件的真实名称
The DATABASE_NAME is the name of the actual database file in the file system,
在我们的例子中是 weather.db
which will be weather.db in our case.
注意我们使用的是版本2  因为课程的这个修订版使用了更新的数据库版本
Note that we're using version 2 since this revision of the course uses
an updated database version.
这些值被传送到构造函数来初始化数据库帮助类
These values get passed into the constructor
to initialize the database helper.
接下来是 onCreate 方法
Next we have the onCreate method.
这是我们讨论的 SQL 和我们新的合约类被一起使用的地方
This is where the SQL we've been talking about and
our new contract class are used together.
数据库被第一次被用到时
The first time the database is used,
SQLiteOpenHelper 的 onCreate 方法被调用
SQLiteOpenHelper's onCreate will be called.
我们需要写正确的SQL语句字符串
We need to write the correct SQL statement string so
这样我们才能创造sunshine需要的表
that we can create the table sunshine needs.
然后系统执行这个 SQL 通过调用 db.execSQL
We then have the system execute this SQL by calling db dot execSQL.
注意我是如何利用所有天气实体常量来写sql语句的
Note how we're using all of the weather entry constants to write our
sequel statements.
同时注意我们在这个表上使用了很多非空约束
Also note that we use lots of not null constraints on this table.
这些约束有助于防止插入未填充列的记录到数据库中  防止bug
These constraints help prevent us from inserting records without columns being
filled out into the database, and that helps to prevent bugs.
这是来自将要创建的位置实体表的 FOREIGN KEY 约束的实现
Here is the implementation of the FOREIGN KEY constraint from the not yet
created location entry table.
这意味必须有一个天气位置的位置实体被插到库里后
This means that we cannot insert a weather entry into the database until
我们才能插入一个天气实体到数据库中
a location entry for the weather location has been inserted.
同时当存在指向位置的天气实体时  我们不能删除位置
And we cannot delete locations while there exist weather
entries that point to them.
话虽这样说  还要等一会我们才能做出UI来展示
That being said, it's going to be a while before we
数据库代码的工作
have UI that can demonstrate that our database code is working.
幸运的是  我们有一个办法让 Android 运行我们想要的任何代码
Fortunately, there's a way we can have Android run any code we want,
甚至没有UI也行
even if there's no UI yet ready.
Android 在测试框架中有一个编译选项允许我们创建测试APK
Android has a built in testing framework that allows us to create a test APK that
执行 JUnit 测试来调用我们主 APK 中的类
executes a JUnit test that call into classes in our main APK.
如果你还不是特别熟悉JUnit
If you aren't already familiar with JUnit,
简单说就是一个允许你写自动测试工具的测试框架
it is a testing framework that allows you to write automated test suites.
你可以很轻易的运行自己的自动测试
You can run your automated tests easily.
你可以在Android Studio 项目节中找到你的测试
You can find your tests in this section of the Android Studio project.
右键测试包并且选择 Run
Just right-click on the test package and select Run.
一旦测试通过或者失败
Once the test pass or
你会看到结果输出在屏幕的底端
fail, you'll see the output down here at the bottom of the screen.
我将不在我们的屏幕上显示模拟器了
I'm not going to display the emulator on our screen because it won't actually
因为它无法真实显示我们做的任何事情
show that we're doing anything.
我们运行的测试没有任何的用户界面
The tests we're running don't have any user interface.
但是在测试运行中你可以看这里  我们正实例化测试
But you can see here in the test runner, we're instantiating tests.
一个空的窗口和绿色的结果意味着测试成功了
An empty window and a green result means the test succeeded.
我们看看 TestPractice 类
Let's look at the TestPractice class.
你可以看到它在我们测试工程的数据包中
You can see it sits in the data package of our test project and
从AndroidTestCase类继承
extends AndroidTestCase.
当你继承 AndroidTestaCase 时
When you extend AndroidTestaCase,
你可以实现 setUp 方法  它会在每次测试前运行
you can implement the setUp method which will be run before each test.
你也可实现 tearDown 方法  它会在每次测试后运行
You can also implement tearDown which we run after each test.
和Junit测试很类似  你只要添加新方法到类中  这些方法以test为前缀
Similar to JUnit test, you simply add new methods in the class with the prefix
例如 testThatDemonstratesAssertions
test such as testThatDemonstratesAssertions.
接下来他们会被测试进程自动的运行
And those will automatically be run by the test processor.
还有些事情要注意的
Some other things to note.
FullTestSuite 类含有这样的代码  包含了所有的在它包里的Java测试类到
The FullTestSuite class contains code to include all of the Java
一个测试工具中  JUnit将会运行这个工具
test classes in its package into a suite of tests the JUnit will run.
这让我们很容易的添加附加测试
This allows us to easily add additional tests,
只需要添加附加的 Java 类文件到我们的测试目录中即可
by just adding additional Java class files to our test directory.
你很有可能在你的每一个测试项目中都有这样一个类
You'll likely have a class like this in each test project you make.
这些类并不是特定项目指定的
They aren't typically project specific.
所以你可以直接拷贝这个类文件
So you can literally just copy this file.
每一个测试至少有一个检查
Each test should have at least one check which uses an assert
检查使用一个 assert（断言） 来查看程序是否应用了正确的输出
to see if the program applies the correct output.
assert就是那样  声明在一部分测试运行
An assert is just that, it's a declaration that
符合我们的预期后的输出
the outcome after part of a test is run matches our expectations.
如果 assert 不匹配  测试失败
If the assert does not match, the test will fail.
我们看看在TestPractice.java类中的testThatDemonstratesAssertions
Let's look at our testThatDemonstratesAssertions in
TestPractice.java.
AssertEquals 确保输出值和实际值相符合
AssertEquals asserts that the expected value equals the actual value.
如果他们不相等  那么一个 assertion 失败的错误
If they are not equal than an assertion failed error is
被带着给出的字符串信息抛出
thrown with the given string message.
其他有用的方法包括assertEquals  assertFalse  assertNull
Other useful methods include assertEquals, assertFalse, assertNull, or
或者如果一个特定代码路径绝对不应被触及时  我们能调用失败
we can just call fail if a certain code path should never have been reached.
随心所欲地写你自己的测试例来运用assertions
Feel free to write your own test cases to play with assertions.
我们来看看当我们做了一个测试失败后发生了什么
Let's see what happens when we make a test fail.
如你所见  结果为红色了
As you can see our results are now red, and
我们可以准确的看到应用在测试的那个地方失败
we can see exactly where in the test are application failed.
让我们在 TestDb 类中把 testCreateDb 函数注释出来
Let's uncomment out the testCreateDb function inside of the TestDb class.
你可能不得不导入一些类使其可编译
You might have to import a few classes to get this to compile.
我们也把 createNorthPoleLocationValues 和 insertNorthPoleLocationValues
Let's also uncomment out the createNorthPoleLocationValues and
从TestUtilities中注释掉
the insertNorthPoleLocationValues functions from within TestUtilities.
如果他们不能编译 这是最后修改你的位置合约的机会
This is the last chance to fix up your location contract if
things don't compile.
让我们用TestDb运行我们新的测试
So let's run our new test with our TestDb.
如你所见  我们得到了一个很好的错误信息返回
As you can see, we get a pretty good error message back, that our database
我们的数据库被创建时缺少位置实体和天气实体表
was created without both the location entry and weather entry tables.
别担心
Don't worry.
我们可以修复它
We can fix it.